<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>KeiSzeto</title>
  
  <subtitle>Constant dropping wears the stone</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://keung.asia/"/>
  <updated>2018-05-30T13:35:00.128Z</updated>
  <id>http://keung.asia/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>KeiSzeto</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>One Hundred Years of Solitude</title>
    <link href="http://keung.asia/posts/35372/"/>
    <id>http://keung.asia/posts/35372/</id>
    <published>2018-05-30T13:23:22.840Z</published>
    <updated>2018-05-30T13:35:00.128Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote class="blockquote-center"><p>Nobel Prize</p></blockquote><p>Nobel Prize winner Gabriel Garcia Marquez passes away at 87</p><p>Nobel Prize winning Colombian writer Gabriel Garcia Marquez passed away Thursday in his home in Mexico City at the age of 87, local media reported.</p><p>Colombian Ambassador to Mexico Jose Gabriel Ortiz confirmed the news.</p><p>The author of the famed novel “One Hundred Years of Solitude,” a groundbreaking work of literature that introduced the world to magic realism, had been checked into a hospital on April 3 to be treated for “dehydration and bronchial and urinary tract infections.”</p><p>Almost a week later, the 1992 Nobel laureate was released into the care of his family, though both doctors and family members acknowledged that his condition was “delicate.”</p><p>Garcia Marquez, who worked as a reporter for many years before dedicating himself to writing fiction, had been living in Mexico City since the 1960s.</p><p>A master of magic realism, along with Latin American writers Julio Cortazar, Juan Rulfo, Carlos Fuentes and Mario Vargas Llosa, Garcia Marquez, wrote numerous well-known novels, including “No One Writes to the Colonel” and “Autumn of the Patriarch.”</p><p>“One Hundred Years of Solitude,” his masterpiece published in 1967, has been translated into 35 languages and sold more than 30 million copies.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      这是我的第一篇博文，就先介绍一下加西亚·马尔克斯作为纪念吧！
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="novel" scheme="http://keung.asia/categories/novel/"/>
    
    
      <category term="百年孤独" scheme="http://keung.asia/tags/%E7%99%BE%E5%B9%B4%E5%AD%A4%E7%8B%AC/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
